Opening
ED
First, second, first, yes
Uh, yes.
Okay, I'll pinch and put them on.
Yes, OK.
Let's go a little bit live with this.
Yes, OK!
Go for it!
Good!
Great pose!
Yes, sir.
Oh, I like it!
Yes, OK!
Go for it!
Yes, cut!
OK, OK!
Yes, OK!
Thank you!
Thank you very much!
I'll see you later today.
Hmm?
Not today.
What do you call this?
Uh, no.
It's not an off-shoot.
What was that?
Watch out for the balloons.
One shot.
No?
What is it?
Looks like they're editing.
Are you looking at the mushroom people?
Mushrooms, maybe.
Watch out for the balloons.
Yes, sir!
Please!
I'm going to go touch my computer.
Stage
Stage.
Yes, I will turn it.
Yes, I'm turning.
Start.
Yes, OK.
Here is the start.
Okay, here we go.
Huh?
Um, pen sai... someone's pen sega popped in the original picture
pen sai, messaai
atos Ng
Hydroponics
Oh, that's nice.
Yes, cut!
Cut!
It's perfect!
It's so good!
I want you to see this!
How's it look? This is it!
It's a great picture!
Have you ever seen a picture with a smile like this?
Wow!
That's a good one.
But I want to put my feet up.
I want to put my feet up.
Shut up!
Let's do the heart of youth.
Feet up!
Yes, thank you very much.
Heart of youth.
Good morning!
I'm taking this video, and the destination is the sky and the fish.
I'm going to put out some doodles here.
I'm filming a journey through the dream world in the lyrics of the song.
And here we go!
And here's the cut!
Just one more time.
It's great, because sometimes the balloons break.
It's very sobering.
Wow!
And then I'm like...
Blue, blue, what's the word?
Uh...
No, like...
It's bluey. I don't know.
It's kind of bluey.
What do you call it? What?
It's a bluey. I'm going to be fine.
I don't know what to say.
I don't know.
Why don't you call me Bluey?
Wow, I want to call him Luke.
Luke.
I don't know what to call him.
I'm curious.
It's Biblouie, the answer is
I'm sorry that all the grownups
I'm sorry you had to think about it.
I'll do my best.
Good job, sir.
Yes, cut! OK, perfect.
We're up and running.
Bang!
This is a surprise, isn't it?
I'm sorry, sir.
Sorry about the earphones.
Thank you very much.
1:30 pm. Finally, the shooting starts. I've been waiting. I'm off.
I've been doing more livestreams lately.
In fact, I've been making a lot of eggs with DD's videos.
And I'm making a lot of dirty faces.
I got a little nervous with the balloons and my ears started to go bad.
My body temperature went up, but I'm glad we managed to finish.
After this, I'm off to take another shot with the four of us. It's fun.
I'm going to have lunch.
Thank you for watching until the end.
After this, I'm going to give you a little ride, and I'm going to ask you to ride in that pose.
Yes, that's good.
Now we're going overseas!
Fun trick work!
Yes, good!
Yes, cut!
Cut!
OK, OK!
We are lip-syncing one lip-sync at a time.
It's too dark, nothing...
Miri is going to start shooting now.
Then what shall we do?
What do you think of me now? I'm going to ask the members what they think of me.
I'm off.
Oh, that sounds good.
Next time notice
We are both eating our lunches right now, but I would like to ask them.
I'm sorry. I just have one question.
What do you think of me?
How do you feel? Are you sick?
You know, just tell me.
I just need you to listen to me a little bit more.
Can I tell you something that's been making me sad lately?
What? What is it?
I just want to be alone.
Why don't you just say it?
No, no, no.
Recently, at the end of a release event, during the last MC announcement.
Yuka mentioned a tour.Yuka was talking about the tour.
Yuka was talking about the tour and the final show was on the 11th.
When Yuka was talking about the tour, he turned to Yurika and said
I tried to say "11" like this three times.
I tried three times, but she ignored me.
You mean you want me to do it with you?
Is it 11? I thought it was a confirmation.
I said yes, yes, yes.
I nodded.
No, by then...
My forehead was all icky from under my nose.
Wait a minute, anyway.
This is the saddest thing I've ever heard.
Let's talk about it.
Look, talk to me. I told you to type, right?
Under the nose!
Please stop!
Ha-ha-ha-ha, all of it!
This is the worst! They might use everything you just said.
Bye bye. I was so sad.
I wanted to ask you something.
What do you think of me?
Are you ashamed of me?
Yes, not at all. Please.
Aren't you ashamed to be asking me that?
I'd like an answer, please.
Yes, I do. It would be nice if we could have a little more conversation.
Are we having a conversation?
We're not having any.
Not the conversation we've been having?
Yes, resonance.
Today, when I was talking to the manager and the staff, I just couldn't come up with an ID.
I kept saying something like blue, but no one could understand me.
I said through this camera that I wanted to call Luca.
The other day when we were going home together, you said something about a weird cloud.
Okay, that's good, that's good.
The clouds.
It conveys the message, the suspicious clouds.
I remember it from the nuance of the kanji.
I remember it.
Yes, yes, yes.
That's right.
And the clouds were a big afterthought. It's weird.
Doubtful is what I remember most.
Thank you.
You said earlier that "small clouds" were "drizzles".
Tiny Thing.
Good-bye.
Okay, I'm going to start drawing.
She was in a motivational pose.
She stopped in a princess pose, looking at the camera.
Ready.
Okay, okay.
Yay!
So cute.
Hand it over to everyone.
Nice face.
How do you like it?
I like it.
It's stylish.
Isn't it pretty?
It's pink and pretty.
I'll fix the mail.
Give it to the others.
Nice face.
I did this part myself.
Pappa catch.
Cute.
It's like a dream hiero.
I wrote Love.
It's cute.
It's cute. It looks like something an elementary school student would wear.
I wrote it because it's cute.
Okay!
Yay!
Let's start!
Smile, everyone!
Smile!
Here we go!
Model!
Whoo!
Wow!
And the camera!
You scared me!
So cute!
It's buried in technology.
Abandoned, which way to go?
Run out your chest like you're breathing
It may never happen again
Stay on top of me
much, much sooner
I can't even feel it
I'll be chosen
Thank you for all your hard work.
I don't know why it's been so uninviting.
I've got this stupid feeling
So let's get erotic
I'm done.
Today's music video shoot ends with a lip, one lip at a time, so I was the first to finish.
I was sad, but, um, I'm sorry.
It was nice, so it's ok.
Thanks for all your hard work - look at a lot of
No garbage in the ramp
Messy words
Wrap it up
Let's eroticize it!
Thank you very much.
Yay!
Let's pass the baton.
Bye bye!
I made a mistake.
It's okay, it was muddy. It was muddy.
I'm glad you said it was perfect.
It's okay that you said that.
Well, it's okay if you said it.
Oh, I'll do my best. I'll do my best.
I look forward to working with you.
Congratulations.
What a surprise, I made a no-miss no-clear. Congratulations.
No clear?
What? No clear?
No clear? No, no, no.
No mistakes. I cleared everything. Thank you very much.
I always have a reputation for not making mistakes in lip-syncing, so I did it again this time. Thank you very much.
I'm going home.
I made a no-mess, no-clear.
Thank you very much.
I'm done.
It's been a long time since I've been able to finish at such a late hour.
It was fun!
It ended with a blue bag!
Thank you very much.
I wish we could have had a little more conversation.
I don't know if that's the conversation we've had so far.
So resonant